[
  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Farrokh Bulsara is the birth name of which celebrity?",
    "options": ["Frank Sinatra", "Freddie Mercury", "Skrillex", "Tiger Woods"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Who is Finn the Human's best friend in Adventure Time?",
    "options": [
      "Lumpy Space Princess",
      "Jake the Dog",
      "Earl of Lemongrab",
      "King of Ooo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "How many teeth does an adult human have?",
    "options": [20, 28, 32, 38],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Which of these UK place names is not real?",
    "options": ["Bell End", "Twatt", "Brown Willy", "Buttonshire"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "What is the capital of Thailand?",
    "options": ["Bangtitz", "Bangkok", "Bangdik", "Bangpusi"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "What was the initial relase year for Dead by Daylight?",
    "options": [2014, 2015, 2016, 2017],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Which shop has the most branches in the UK?",
    "options": ["Greggs", "KFC", "Burger King", "McDonald's"],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notes": [
      "McDonalds: 1439",
      "KFC: 1016",
      "Burger King: 526",
      "Greggs: 2269",
      "Data from scrapehero.com"
    ]
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Blender is a free open source software used to creating what?",
    "options": [
      "YouTube thumbnails",
      "Virtual Machines",
      "Musical playlists",
      "3D computer graphics"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Which YouTube channel has the most subsribers of all time?",
    "options": ["T-Series", "WWE", "PewDiePie", "MrBeast"],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notes": [
      "T-Series 2nd: 267M",
      "WWE 10th: 102M",
      "PewDiePie 8th: 111M",
      "MrBeast 1st: 281M"
    ]
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Vernor Winfield MacBriare Smith IV is the birth name of which celebrity?",
    "options": [
      "Matthew McConaughey",
      "Ewan McGregor",
      "Mac Demarco",
      "Seth MacFarlane"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Who was Doctor Who's 12th Doctor?",
    "options": [
      "Peter Capaldi",
      "Matt Smith",
      "Jodie Whittaker",
      "David Tennant"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "On average, how much does a 30 second Super Bowl advert cost?",
    "options": ["$5Million", "$10Million", "$20Million", "$2.5Million"],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notes": [
      "According to  https://parade.com/living/super-bowl-commercial-cost"
    ]
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "How many stripes on the flag of the USA?",
    "options": [13, 14, 15, 16],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Straight Answer",
    "question": "What is the capital of New Zeland?",
    "correctAnswer": "Wellington"
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "What does USB stand for?",
    "options": [
      "Unified System Buffer",
      "Uninterrupted Signal Bus",
      "Universal System Bus",
      "Universal Serial Bus"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "Which of these have the most followers?",
    "options": [
      "PSY (psy_oppa)",
      "Snoop Dogg (SnoopDogg)",
      "Kendrick Lamar (KendrickLamar)",
      "Ed Sheeran (edsheeran)"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notes": [
      "PSY 4.1M",
      "Snoop Dogg 20.7M",
      "Kendrick Lamar 12.7",
      "Ed Sheeran 16.8"
    ]
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "How many times have the UK scored 0 in the Eurovision song contest?",
    "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notes": ["2003 with Gemini: Cry Baby", "2021 with James Newman: Embers"]
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Straight Answer",
    "question": "Which archnemesis of Mario first appeard in the 1992 Super Mario Land 2: 6 Golden Coins as the final boss?",
    "correctAnswer": "Wario"
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Multiple Choice",
    "question": "What European country experienced the highest rate of population decline from 2015 - 2020?",
    "options": ["Wales", "Italy", "Lithuania", "Germany"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Naughty by Nature"],
    "title": "O.P.P.",
    "alternativeTitles": ["OPP", "O.P.P"],
    "alternativeArtists": {}
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Post Malone", "21 Savage"],
    "title": "rockstar",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": {}
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Lenny Kravitz"],
    "title": "Fly Away",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": {}
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["boy pablo"],
    "title": "Losing you",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": {}
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Michael Jackson"],
    "title": "Thriller",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": {
      "Michael Jackson": ["MJ", "M.J.", "M.J", "Micheal Jackson"]
    }
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Dance Gavin Dance"],
    "title": "The Ghost of Billy Royalton",
    "alternativeTitles": ["Ghost of Billy Royalton"],
    "alternativeArtists": { "Dance Gavin Dance": ["Dance, Gavin Dance"] }
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Tame Impala"],
    "title": "Lost in Yesterday",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": {}
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["The Weeknd"],
    "title": "I feel it coming",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": { "The Weeknd": ["The Weekend", "Weekend", "Weeknd"] }
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Gorillaz", "Shaun Ryder"],
    "title": "Dare",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": {
      "Gorillaz": ["Gorillas", "Gorilaz", "Gorilas"]
    }
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Mac Demarco"],
    "title": "Chamber of Reflection",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": {}
  },

  {
    "questionType": "Music Round",
    "artists": ["Daft Punk", "Pharrell Williams"],
    "title": "Get Lucky",
    "alternativeTitles": [],
    "alternativeArtists": { "Pharrell Williams": ["Pharrell"] }
  }
]
